(Sheldon:)Because it made me realize
they'll just send anyone up there.
(Sheldon:)-Aren't you going to let me out?
-No.
(Sheldon:)But I still need to use the bathroom.
(Howard:)Here you go. Be creative.
(Howard:)What's the matter?
Scared of a little turbulence?
(Sheldon:)No, turbulence is
just the equalization
(Sheldon:)of diurnal temperature
variations in the atmosphere.
(Sheldon:)I'm not scared at all.
(Sheldon:)Oh, apple juice,
stay where you are.
(Howard:)Oh, this is nothing.
I experienced way worse
(Howard:)when I was plummeting
back to Earth,
(Howard:)apparently not being
a real astronaut.
Okay, that was a big ons.
(Sheldon:)I take it back.
I'm scared of turbulence!
(Howard:)I'm gonna need that bag back.
(Leonard:)You sure you want to do this?
(Penny:)Yeah. Why wouldn't I want
to get my old job back?
(Penny:)It'll be fun to see everyone.
(Penny:)I haven't talked to them
since I said, "I quit.
See you at the Oscars, bitches."